var questions = [{
    question: "what was the name of the first disney movie ever made?",
    correctAnswer: "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs",
    answers: [
        {
            content: "Mickey Mouse"
        },
        {
            content: "Lion King"
        },
        {
            content: "Aladan"
        },
        {
            content: "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs",
        },
    ]
},
{
    question: "In what year was the first Disney movie releasaed?",
    correctAnswer: "The first Disney movie was release in In 1937.",
    answers: [
        {
            content: "Mickey Mouse"
        },
        {
            content: "The first Disney movie was release in In 1937."
        },
        {
            content: "Aladan"
        },
        {
            content: "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs",
        },
    ]
},
{
    question: "What type of movie was the first Disney movie?",
    correctAnswer: "It was an animated movie",
    answers: [
        {
            content: "Mickey Mouse"
        },
        {
            content: "The first Disney movie was release in In 1937."
        },
        {
            content: "It was an animated movie."
        },
        {
            content: "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs"
        },
    ]
},
{
    question: "In what year was the Lawrenceville Prep school founded?",
    correctAnswer: "The Lawrenceville Prep school was founded in 1810.",
    answers: [
        {
            content: "The Lawrenceville Prep school was founded in 1810."
        },
        {
            content: "The Lawrenceville School is a coeducational, independent college preparatory boarding school for students in ninth through twelfth grades including a post-graduate year as well. Lion King"
        },
        {
            content: "Therea are Students: 816 students"
        },

        {
            content: "Maidenhead Academy"
        },

        {
            content: "1881",
        },
    ]
},
{
    question: "Who is played Mary Poppins?",
    correctAnswer: "Mary Poppins is played by British actress Julie Andrews. ",
    answers: [
        {
            content: "Mary Poppins was based on Pamela Lyndon Travers."
        },
        {
            content: "Mary Poppins was releasaed in 1964."
        },
        {
            content: "Mary Poppins is played by British actress Julie Andrews. ",
        },
        {
            content: "When was Mary Poppins Release?"
        },
    ]
},
{
    question: "Name 3 cast members and their roles in the Lion King Movie?",
    correctAnswer: "Donald Glover as Simba, James Al Jones as Musafa and Billy Eschiner as Timon.",
    answers: [
        {
            content: "July 19, 2019."
        },
        {
            content: "There are 3."
        },
        {
            content: "Donald Glover as Simba, James Al Jones as Musafa and Billy Eschiner as Timon."
        },
        {
            content: "Who inspired the story of the Lion King?"
        },
    ]
},
{
    question: "Who founded New Jersey?",
    correctAnswer: "New Jersey was founded by Sir John Berkeley and Sir George Carteret.",

    answers: [
        {

            content: "New Jersey."
        },

        {

            content: "New Jersey was named for Jersey, the largest of the British Channel Islands."
        },

        {

            content: "New Jersey was founded by Sir John Berkeley and Sir George Carteret."

        },

        {

            content: "CaGeorge Carteret born?"
        },
    ]

},
{
    question: "In what year was the Constitution written?",
    CorrectAnswer: "September 17, 1787.",

    answers: [
        {
            content: "The committee included Jefferson, Benjamin Franklin, John Adams, Robert Livingston, and Roger Sherman. Robert Livingston"
        },

        {
            content: "September 17, 1787."
        },

        {
            content: "Who is the founder of New Jersey?"

        },

        {
            content: "Where was Sir George Carteret born?"
        },
    ]
},
{
    question: "Who founded New Jersey?",
    correctAnswer: "New Jersey was founded by Sir John Berkeley and Sir George Carteret.",

    answers: [
        {
            content: "New Jersey."
        },

        {
            content: "New Jersey was named for Jersey, the largest of the British Channel Islands."
        },

        {
            content: "New Jersey was founded by Sir John Berkeley and Sir George Carteret."

        },

        {
            content: "CaGeorge Carteret born?"
        },
    ]
},
{
    question: "How many members are there in Congress in total?",
    correctAnswer: "There are a total of 535 Members of Congress.",
    answers: [

        {
            content: "There are 435 members"
        },

        {
            content: "There are a total of 535 Members of Congress."
        },
        {
            content: "Federal law, passed on Aug. 8, 1911, that measure raised the number of representatives to 435 from 391"
        },
        {
            content: "There are 100 Senators in the Senate."
        },
    ],
},

{
    question: "Who are 5 of Vogue's 10 Best Dressed Women Of 2018?",
    correctAnswer: "Tracee Ellis Ross, Lady Gaga, The Duchess of Sussex, ZoÃ« Kravitz and Zendaya",
    answers: [
        {
            content: "Tracee Ellis Ross, Lady Gaga, Dione Warwick and Mary Rogers."
        },
        {
            content: "Violette James, Stacey Wills, May Nevers, Jason Mees and Royal."
        },
        {
            content: "Jennifer Williams, Vivianille, Jonas Sisters, and Logan Perry Wils"
        },
        {
            content: "Who are 5 of Vogue's 10 Best Dressed Women Of 2018?"
        },
    ]
}
]
